# PRANALI JOURAS JEP Coach

Mumbai, MH 400051 • 966 408 6161 • pranalijouras510@gmail.com

## **Professional Summary**

Financial specialist with a strong belief in good performance comes with discipline and using a master strategy of working smart. Understanding customer's financial situation, giving them the appropriate solutions and collecting on the chase credit cards. Assisting the team manager with various aspects like driving performance, utilization, reports, etc.

Completed a Product management course from Duke University with a number of new processes learnt like:

Google Anaytics

**SQL** 

Whimsical

Wirify

MarvelApp

**AppyPie** 

Agile

Scrum, to mention a few.

#### Skills

Communications

Relationship development

Brand development

Product management

Structural approach

Business Intelligence

Product management

# **Work History**

JEP Coach, 07/2019 to Current

JP Morgan Chase – Mumbai, Maharashtra

Currently a JEP coach training and mentoring a team of 15 individuals, and helping them with performance, managing CSAT and shareholder, and helping in raising accesses.

- Worked with Chase card customers to understand needs and provide excellent service.
- To provide solutions based on customer's current financial situations including programs with

benefits, etc.

- Managing collections and maintaining a score card .
- Assisting the team to improve their performance
- Managing the team's utilization

Assisted the bottom quartile individuals and helped them to manage and excel in shareholder metrics and CSAT.

## Senior Customer Service Executive, 02/2018 to 06/2019

Teleperformance – Mumbai, Maharashtar

- Resolved Barclays bank issues by clarifying customer's complaints, determining causes of problems and selecting best solutions.
- Answered multi-line phones and used active listening skills to assess client's issues and challenges.
- Evaluated customer information to explore issues, develop potential solutions and maintain high-quality service.
- Responded to customer inquiries and queries to provide thorough and speedy resolutions.
- Collaborated with staff members to enhance customer service experience and exceed team goals through effective client satisfaction rates.
- Met all customer call guidelines including service levels, handle time and productivity.

#### **Educator and Mentor**, 12/2016 to 02/2018

DGT Classes – Mumbai, Maharashtra

- Collaborated with adults and children to provide safe and educational experience.
- Chose materials and developed lesson plans to enhance skills for individual students.
- Assisted with development of improved seminars and training materials.
- Taught subjects like English, Mathematics and Science and mentored them to build a promising career.

## Business Development Officer, 06/2016 to 11/2016

**Appco** – Mumbai, Maharashtra

Branding and Advertising for blue chip companies .

- Generated new business with marketing initiatives and strategic plans.
- Collaborated with sales and marketing departments to support business objectives and client acquisition.
- Supervised team of 3 and worked together with them to strategize marketing and branding tactics and helping them become better at it.
- Building good customer relationships with clients and customers to build and enhance a long term relationship.

•

#### **Education**

Bachelor's in Enineering: Information Technology
Universal College Of Engineering - Mumbai, Bandra
Graduated from Universal college of Engineering with a 6.75 CGPA

he file of study Information Technology.

Worked on a paper called gesture based audio/video player in IEEE.

Hosted a number of events in college and was the head of departments like: Marketing,

Magazine, Fun Games, etc. for the technical inter college festival at our very own college.

**Higher Secondary HSC**: Science **Sathaye College** - Vile Parle, Mumbai

Secondary School Certificate

Duruelo Convent High School - Bandra , Mumbai

# **Accomplishments**

Have completed a full fledged diploma course in **Advanced Digital Marketing**. Also initiated a cause called **vowforchange**, and with the help of **Google ads**, **analytics and keyword planner**, **created ads on Google**, **facebook** and **Instagram**, with almost **80k clicks and leads** generated through the marketing campaigns.

## **Certifications**

Advanced digital marketing

Product management certificate program from Upgrad

#### **Interests**

Working and developing my cause 'vowforchange

Learning about Astronomy

Building a platform for vocational training

Editing and creating attractive banners